ANVIT DUBEY

+(91) 8004509825 \(\phi\) anvdub29@gmail.com LinkedIn \(\phi\) Github \(\phi\) Stack-Overflow \(\phi\) Medium

ABOUT

Highly skilled Computer Scientist with experience of creating responsive and user-friendly websites and improving website's performance through optimization and testing. Excellent communication and teamwork skills, with a passion for staying up-to-date with the latest technologies and trends.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Science, Kalinga Institute of Industrial Technology (2020-2024) CGPA: 9.0

Secondary School, City Montessori School (2018-2020)

EXPERIENCE

Peer-Peer Learning (KIIT)

March 2023 - May 2023

Score: 92%

- Provided guidance and support to more than 500+ students in Web technologies
- · Created and lead weekly workshops to introduce new concepts and provide hands-on experience

Freelancer (AMB LKO Foundation)

Jan 2023 - Feb 2023

Lucknow. India

- Assessed UI/UX designs for technical feasibility developed with Material-UI for the organization.
- Tech stack used: ReactJs, Spring Boot, AWS.

PROJECTS

Travel Map Notes: Developed intuitive **MERN Stack** app for travel enthusiasts using **Mapbox and React Hooks** & **MongoDb & Express** for back-end. Features geolocation, map-based notes, data sync which enhances their travel experiences.

Algorithm Visulizer: Algorithm visualization tool to help explain complex algorithms and data structures. The project is based on **ReactJs MaterialUi**, and utilized **ChartJs** to create visual representations of algorithms.

IPL Dashboard: Web application for cricket fans to get information about IPL in an enterprise-level dashboard. The project is based on **Spring MVC architecture** which uses **Spring Boot, React and AWS** for the website:.

SKILLS

Technical Stack ReactJs, MaterialUi, JDBC, MySql, Ci/Cd

Tools AWS, Docker, Kubernetes, Postman, Git, Firebase, Android Studio, VsCode

Languages JavaScript, CSS, Html, Java, Sql, Golang, Python

Interests Problem Solving, Cloud, Operating Systems, DBMS, Computer Networks

CERTIFICATES/ ACHIEVEMENTS

- LeetCode: Solved 450+ questions and achieved monthly LeetCoding challenge badges.
- · Google HashCode-2020: Ranked 3rd in the whole university.
- Goldman Sachs Engineering Program: Cracked leak password database using md5 & SHA algorithm.

CO-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

- Leadership(Organization): Served as the Lead of Microsoft Learn Student Ambassador back at college.
- Events Organized: Organized and lead multiple events and workshop with an audience of more than 5000 students in offline mode.
- Volunteer Experience: Taught Java as a tutor on KIIT Buzz(YouTube Channel).